안녕하세요, 척이에요
아셔야 할 게 있어요.
Hi, I'm chuck. Here are a few things
that you might need to know.
질
Jill.
Hey
내가 도와줄게
I can help you.
Come on
질, 널 체포한다
그리고 우리 헤어져
You're under arrested, Jill,
and I'm breaking up with you.
아빠가 떠났어
아빠 손을 잡고 결혼하고 싶었어
Dad's gone. I thought I needed
him to walk me down the aisle.
아빠가 우릴 떠났지만
지금은 다를 거라 생각했어
I thought that he would be different
from that guy that walked out on us.
걱정 마렴, 너도
나에 대해 잘못 알고 있으니까
Don't worry, Charles.
I'm not who you think I am.
무사하셨군요
You all right.
풀크럼 인터섹트도 만들게
대신 내 아들은 보내줘
I'll give FULCRUM their Intersect,
but my son walks away from here.
잘 지내거라
Take care of yourself.
아빠가 인터섹트를
새로 만들면
As soon as my dad
finishes the new Intersect,
제가 필요없게 될테고
풀크럼이 이기게 될 거예요
I'm worthless to you
and FULCRUM wins.
지금 중요한 건
아빠를 구하는 거예요
The only thing that matters now
is getting my father back.
이거 먹어봐요
Fro yo?
오바마 구아바라고
신제품이에요
It's time to try our latest flavor, Obama Guava.
이름 내가 만든 거 아니에요
I didn't make up the name.
아뇨 됐어요
no, thanks.
CIA가 새 레시피를 찾아서
저도 좋긴 한데요
Not that I'm not thrilled that
the CIA has found a new yogurt recipe, I was just...
레시피 보단 우리 아빨
먼저 찾아줄 거라 생각했거든요
I don't know, kind of hoping
the CIA would find my father first.
정부에서 최선을 다해서
찾고 있어요
The government is doing everything
they can to find him.
그 사람들을 어떻게 믿어요?
How do I know I can trust them?
인터섹트도 내 머리에
넣고 싶어서 넣은 거 아니였잖아요
The government wasn't
to keep the Intersect in my head.
아빠만이 날 도울 수 있어요
최선을 다한다고 될 일이 아니라고요
My father is only person who can get it out.
It's not rocket science.
그 사람들 안 믿는 거 알아요
하지만 난 믿죠?
Okay, I know that you don't trust them,
but do you trust me?
네
Yeah.
고마워요, 내가 약속할게요
꼭 찾아낼 게요
Good. Then I promise you, we're going to find him.
네, 서둘러줘요
Well, hurry, please.
척, 뭐가 문제야?
What's the matter, Chuck?
아빤 다시 돌아오셨지
Your dad's back in town, right?
엄청 섹시한 여자랑 사귀지
You're dating the hottest slice of the proverbial pizza,
게다가 나랑 베프잖아
and you are best friends with me...
내 말은 셋 중 두 가지는
그리 나쁘지 않잖아?
Which means two out of three ain't so bad, right?
넌 이 세상의 왕이나 다름 없다고
Come on, You're king of the world, dude.
바토스키, 잘 들어
Bartowski, get it together.
그래, 퍽도 왕이다
Yeah. King of the world.
에멧이 할 말이 있댄다
Emmett's got an announcement.
그러니 잘 들어!
So listen up!
맞습니다, 캡틴
Aye, aye, captain.
자, 지금부터 24시간 내에
All right, now,
some time over the next 24 hours,
바이모어 평가자가 와서
바로 이 몸을 평가할 거예요
a Buy More corporate evaluator
will be here to evaluate your truly.
보통 이런 경우에는
Now, normally, in this situation,
일부러 날 깍아내리려고 하는
I would expect a certain tribe
사람들이 있다는 거 알아요
to use this opportunity to make me look bad.
다들 맘껏 웃어요
Laugh it up, cretins.
인도에서 "감자 튀김이랑
음료수도 드릴까요?"
The tech jobs are being shipped
to India faster than you can say,
하면서 일하고 싶으면
맘껏 웃어요
"Would you like fries
and a soft drink with that?"
전 패스트 푸드 점에서 일 못해요
I can't work fast food, Emmett.
율법에 어긋나요
I... keep kosher.
인도 갈 때 나도 껴줘요
Count me in on the trip to India.
레스터가 고향에서
지내는 거 직접 보고 싶었어요
I've always dreamt of seeing Lester in his native environment.
뭐?
What?
날 시험하려 했다간
You test me
평생을 불쌍하게 햄버거
만들다 죽을 줄 알아요
and you'll be flipping burgers in Encino
for the rest of your miserable life.
자, 그러니 사람들에게
Now...
Let's show corporate
우리가 얼마나
열심히 일하는지 보여줍시다
that we are a lean, mean, Buy More machine.
- 머리 좀 빗고
- 부러워서 그러지
-So, comb your hair.
-Jealous.
창녀처럼 올려입지 말고
Lower that whore skirt.
뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
그리고 제발 부탁이에요
And for God's sakes, Barnes,
엉덩이 그만 보고 싶으니까
I am tired of seeing your butt crack.
올려 입어요
Pull them up!
잘됐다
Well, that went well.
장군님한테 연락이 왔어
Hey. Update from Beckman.
뭐라세요?
What?
아빠가 어딨는지 알아냈대요?
Is it information about where my father is?
가서 들어보자
We’re about to find out.
너네 내 피부에
튀긴 음식이 얼마나 안 좋은지 알아?
I mean, people,
do you have any idea
what working with fried food
would do to my complexion?
난 꼭 바이모어에서 일해야 돼
I can't leave the Buy More.
바깥 세상에선
살아남지 못 할 거야
I won't survive in the real world.
여기에 너무 익숙해졌어
I'm institutionalized.
모건, 우리 둘이
이번 작전의 축이야
Morgan, we are the brain of this operation.
너랑 내가 뭔가 좋은 수를 내야 해
So, let's you and I come up with something.
어떻게 하면 좋을까?
Why don't you start us off?
글쎄, 내 생각에는
Well, as I see it,
우리가 열심히 일하라고
협박한 걸 거야
Emmett's threat was a ruse to get us to work hard,
그래야 본인이
본사에 점수를 딸 테니까
so he would look good in front of corporate.
하지만 이걸 생각해봐
But think about this.
우리한테 똑바로 처신하라고 한 건
Emmett asked us to behave because he knows
우리가 똑바로 처신하지
않을 거란 걸 알고 있기 때문이야
we would do the exact opposite--
we'd misbehave.
하지만 에멧은 바보가 아니니까
분명히 자기 의도가
But Emmett, eh,
he's no fool, so he would know
뭔지 우리가 알고 있을 거란 걸
알고 있을 거야
that we would know that he knows this.
그니까 우린
똑바로 처신해야 해
So, obviously, we need to behave.
그래, 그럼 잘하자
Okay, so we behave.
집중해서 들어
그 반대야
Pay attention. It's the exact opposite.
또 우리가 알고 있단 걸
에멧이 안단 걸 우리가 안다고 생각할 거야
Emmett would also know
that we'd know that he knows we know,
왜냐면 우리보고 잘하길
바란다고 한 걸
because he knows that we know that what he knows
우리가 알고 있다고 알고 있으니까
is that we know he wants us to behave.
그래!
Right!
맞아!
Yes!
뭘 안다는 건지 모르겠지만
우린 진짜 천재야
Yes. I don't know how we do it,but we are geniuses, my friend.
고마워
Thank you.
그니까 어떻게 한다는 거야?
So, what are we doing again?
역시 과학 기술이 최고라니까
God, I love technology.
그니까 우리의 계획은
What we are doing again
로마를 불태우는 거야
is we're going to let Rome burn.
가능한 방법을 모두 동원해서
We've used every resource
찾아봤지만 찾을 수가 없었네
to find him with no luck.
미안하네, 척
I'm sorry, Chuck.
풀크럼에서 행방을
철저히 비밀에 부치고 있어
FULCRUM's kept a tight lid on your father's whereabouts.
그래서 부르셨어요?
That's your update?
죄송하지만
특별한 얘기도 아닌 거 같은데요
Well, I'm sorry, but that's a non-update.
이 정도론 택도 없다고요
And you know what?It's not good enough.
입 조심해
장군님한테 무슨 말버릇이야
Watch it, Bartowski.It's a U.S.
general you're talking to.
난 지난 1년 동안
I've spent the last year of my life
고문 당하고
고층 건물에서 떨어질 뻔하고
being tortured, dangled off of skyscrapers,
하수구에 빠져 살았어요
bathed in sewage.
내가 까먹은 다른 재밌었던
일 있으면 어디 한번 말해봐요
Stop me if I've forgotten
any other glamorous perks of this job.
난 그동안 당신들이 시켜온 일이면
I've continually done everything
뭐든 군말없이 다 했어요
that you guys have asked me to do,
근데 우리 아빠가 납치당했는데
but once my dad gets kidnapped,
기껏 한다는 말이 미안하다 뿐이에요?
all you can say is sorry?
척, 자네가 상심한 거 알고 있네
Chuck, I understand your disappointment
정말 아세요? 근데 왜 아직도
우리 아빨 못 찾으셨어요?
Do you? Then why haven't we found him yet?
예전에 잡았던 풀크럼 요원들한테
물어보면 되잖아요?
We've captured FULCRUM agents before. Can't we talk to them?
그것도 시도해봤지만 새 정권에서
Yeah, we tried that, but since the new administration
물 고문 중지 명령이 내려와서
입을 열 방법이 없어
discontinued water-boarding, FULCRUM agents don't talk.
그리고 입을 연다고 해도
그 말을 믿어야 할지도 문제고요
And even if we did, we have no reason to trust them.
난 필요하다면
뭐든 할 준비가 되어있어요
I'm willing to do whatever it takes
by any means necessary.
내가 만약 풀크럼 요원
입을 열게 할 수 있다면요?
So what if I could get a FULCRUM agent to talk?
이렇게 해도
정말로 괜찮겠어요?
You're 100% sure you want to go through with this?
어느 정도는요
More like 45,
안 괜찮을 것 같기도 하고
maybe... maybe 30.
하지만 이거 외에
별다른 방법이 없잖아요?
But I guess I don't really have any other choice now, do I?
안녕, 척
Hi, Chuck.
안녕, 질
Hello, Jill.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
빡沽쇌딴莖꼽뎔 뒤랗센뒤20섞
-=팎읔襟俚캥莉=-
珂쇌菉：襟소팍
영어자막
http://www.ragbear.com
한글자막
김호정 (hojeong_@nate.com)
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요
그래, 음식은 어때?
So, how's the food?
보통 감옥 음식이야
아님 좀 더 특별한 맛이야?
Standard prison issue, or are they doing anything fancy
with the sauces?
척, 여긴 왜 온 거야?
What are you doing here, Chuck?
풀크럼에서 아빠를 납치했어
FULCRUM has kidnapped my father.
아빠한테 인터섹트를
다시 만들게 하고 있어
They're using him to rebuild their Intersect,
그리고 다 완성되면..
and when he's done...
그 땐 어떻게 될지
생각하고 싶지도 않아
Look, I don't even want to think
about what's gonna happen when that happens.
내가 맞춰 볼까
Let me guess.
도와달라고 왔구나?
You want my help?
싫어
Forget it.
나한테 화난 거 알아
I get that you're mad at me,
하지만 네가 여깄는 게
나 때문은 아니잖아
but it's not my fault you're in here.
네가 조국을 배신했기 때문이지
You betrayed your country.
날 배신하기도 했고
Who betrayed me.
난 네가 날 좋아하는 줄 알았어
I thought you cared about me, but now,
내 가족을 되찾을 수 있게 도와줘
all I'm asking is formy family back, please.
내가 도와줄 수도 있어
I might be able to help.
하지만 거래를 해
But I want a deal.
Uh...
안 돼, 들어준다고 하지마
Do not make a deal. Do not make a deal!
내가 내 맘대로
말할 수 있는 위치가 아냐
I'm-I'm not... I'm not really authorized
to make any kind of deal.
하지만 이번엔
예외를 둬도 괜찮겠지
But in this case, I think
I can make an exception.
여기 직원이냐고요?
아뇨
Do I work here? No, no.
당신같은 사람들이 물어볼까봐
I just wear this ridiculous outfit
일부러 이런 우스꽝스러운
옷을 입고 다니는 거예요
so that people like you will ask me if I do.
에멧이 너한테 전해 주래
Emmett asked me to give this to you.
Oh.
그거 재밌겠다
Mighty fine cart work.
에멧?
Emmett?
저기요?
Hello?
여기 쪽지 받고 왔는데
Got this... Got this note.
에멧
Milbarge.
모건
Grimes.
본론부터 말하죠
Let me cut to the chase.
난 당신이 정말 싫어요
I despise you.
하지만 저 찌질이들이
당신 말은 들으니까 날 도와줘야겠어요
But these losers listen to you for some reason, so I need you.
말해봐요 / 난 여길 효율적으로
운영하기 위해 파견된 사람이에요
Talk to me. I was brought here to make this store efficient.
본사에서 지금 이 꼴을 보면
If corporate sees that, they will have no recourse
제대로 운영되고 있지 않단 걸 알고
but to do the efficient thing
이 지옥 구덩이에서 빼내주겠죠
and promote me out of this hellhole.
당신의 기쁨조 친구들이
제대로만 해준다면
Get your little merry band of misfits
to behave, and I'll be out of your dirty beard forever.
나랑은 영원히 볼 일 없을 거예요
당신을 믿어야 할지 어떻게 알아요?
How do I know that I can... trust you?
모르죠
난 이제 여길 떠나고 싶어요
You don't, but I want out,
당신도 내가 나가길 바랄테니..
and you want me out, so let's...
거래해요
...make a deal.
내가 이런 거래를 하게 되다니
I can't believe we made this deal.
도망치거나 배신하면
If you run or double-cross us,
거래는 무효화 되고
거기에 보너스로
your deal is void. Plus, as an added bonus,
쟤가 널 쏴버릴 거야
she'll shoot you.
척 아버지는 어디에 있지?
Chuck's dad- where is he?
확실하게는 몰라요
I don't know exactly,
하지만 그걸 알 만한 사람은 알아요
but I do know someone
who might know where they're holding him.
누군데? / 버니 삼촌
Who? My Uncle Bernie.
장난은 그만 두는 게 좋을 거야
That better not be a joke,
난 유머감각 따윈 없으니까
'cause I don't have a sense of humor.
그래, 우리 사귈 때 버니라는
Yeah, I don't remember you ever mentioning
삼촌이 있다고 한번도 말한 적 없잖아
an Uncle Bernie to mewhen we were dating.
진짜 삼촌이 아니니까
He's not a real uncle.
우리 가족하고 친한 분이셔
He's a friend of the family.
날 풀크럼으로 스카우트 한
사람도 삼촌이야
He's the one who first recruited me into FULCRUM.
그 사람을 어떻게 믿죠?
And how do we know we can trust him?
아빠랑 제일 친한 친구니까요
He's my dad's best friend.
세상에서 한 명만 믿어야 한다면
난 그 분을 믿겠어요
If there's one person I can trust, it's him.
어디 있는데?
Where's Bernie?
우리가 잡아다가
입 열 때까지 고문할 거야
We'll flush him out,
torture the location out of him.
하루의 거의 대부분은
보디가드랑 같이 있어요
He's guarded almost 24 hours a day.
'거의'라니 무슨 뜻이에요?
What does almost mean?
그래, 그럼 언제 혼자 있는데?
Yeah, when is Bernie away from his bodyguards?
식구들한테 일이 있을 때
Usually only for family functions.
곧 모일 일 없어?
Are there any coming up?
생일이나 성인식, 파티 같은 거?
Birthdays, confirmations, quiceaneras?
그래, 그럼..
Well, then,
우리가 직접 하나 만들어야겠네
I guess we're going to have to create one on our own.
저 약혼했어요
I'm engaged.
타코리 제품이래요
It's Tacori.
정말 예쁘다
It's beautiful.
고맙습니다, 주디
Oh, well, thanks, Judy.
아냐, 어머니라고 하렴
No, call me Mom.
여자들은 다이아 반지로
4가지 C를 얻는다고들 하잖아요
Most women only get four C's with a ring,
하지만 질은
5가지를 얻었어요
but, uh, my Jill- she got five.
가공상태, 색깔, 깨끗함, 크기
그리고 척이요
Cut, color, clarity, carat, and Chuck.
너무 예쁘지 않아요?
Isn't this gorgeous?
국민들 피땀으로 산 반지야
That ring cost the taxpayers
a fortune, Bartowski.
잃어 버리지마
Don't lose it.
여기들 있었구나
Here they are.
바토스키 부부!
Mr. and Mrs.Bartowski.
* Good day ??????????*
질, 그나저나
우리가 얼마자 놀랐는 줄 아니
So, Jill, this is such a wonderful surprise.
우린 네가 헬싱키에
있는 줄 알았어
We thought she was living in Helsinki. We...
다시 보게 될 줄 몰랐구나
We didn't know when we'd see her again.
척이 프로포즈를 해서
Well, Chuck popped the question,
모두에게 알리고 싶었어요
and I wanted to share it with everybody.
월리, 이제 우리
축배를 들어요
Well, Wally,
I think this calls for a toast.
아녜요 아빠
No, no, no, Dad.
안 그러셔도 돼요
You don't... You don't have to do that.
우리 공주님이 결혼하는 날을
Listen, I have waited all my life
내가 얼마나 손꼽아 기다렸는데
for my little girl to get married-
당연히 축배를 들어야지
you bet I do.
너희가 스탠포드에서
처음 만난 날이 생각나는구나
I remember when you first met at Stanford,
서로를 바라보는 그 눈빛..
the way you'd look at each other...
꼭 네 엄마와 날 보는 듯 했어
Just like your mom and I did.
둘 사이가
항상 좋았던 건 아니지만
And I know you've had your problems,
마음 깊은 곳에선
but deep inside,
서로가 서로의 짝이란 걸
알았던 거야
you knew you were right for each other.
앞으로는 항상
행복하게 지내렴
And you never let anything get in the way of that.
질과 척을 위해
To Jill and Chuck.
질과 척을 위하여!
To Jill and Chuck!
축하한다, 바토스키
Congratulations, Bartowski.
이제 배우자 면회 할 수 있겠다
You're now qualified for conjugal visits.
차가 들어오고 있어
There's a car approaching.
그 남자일 거야
This could be him.
바토스키
인간 병기나 다름 없는 자야
Bartowski, this guy's a madman.
암호명이 '육식동물'이야
His codename's "The Carnivore."
피를 좋아하는 놈인 거 같아
Seems he's got a real appetite
for blood.
잘됐네요
Great.
버니, 잘 지냈나?
Hey, Bernie, how are you?!
아주 잘 지냈지
Great, Wally.
그래, 전화로는 할 수 없다는
So, what is this big surprise
깜짝 뉴스가 대체 뭐야?
you couldn't tell me over the phone?
질이 약혼했어!
Jill's engaged!
질이 여기 있어?
Jill's here?
어디?
Where?
너 정말 귀엽다, 척
You are so adorable, Chuck.
너희가 아이를 낳으면
정말 예쁠 거야
You two are gonna have the most beautiful babies.
아들, 딸 하나씩 있으면 좋겠어
I want a girl and a boy.
미안하구나 척
내가 아이 얘기해서 겁먹었니?
I'm sorry, Chuck, is allthis talk of children
scaring you?
아뇨, 저 아이들 좋아해요
정말로요
No, no, no, I love kids, really, yeah.
질!
JILL!
네가 헬싱키로 이사간 줄 알았어
I thought you moved to Helsinki.
저희도 그랬어요, 버니
You're not the only one, Bernie.
너 정말 집에 자주 좀 들러
You really need to come home more often.
맞아요, 저도 얼굴 보기가 힘들다니까요
Yeah, I-I barely get to see her myself.
일을 너무 많이 해요
감옥에 있는 거나 마찬가지에요
She works so much, she might as well be in prison.
그래 자네가 그 행운아로구만?
Oh, so you're the lucky guy, huh?
네
Oh, hey!
안녕하세요
척이라고 합니다, 버니
It's Chuck, nice to meet you, Bernie.
아냐 아냐
No, no, no.
버니 삼촌이라고 부르게
You call me Uncle Bernie.
이제 우린 한 가족이야
We're family now.
행복한 결혼생활을 위해선
서로에 대한
We were just telling them that the key
신뢰가 필수란
얘길 하고 있었네
to a good marriage is trust.
배우자는 네가 항상
의지할 수 있는 유일한 사람이자
Your spouse must be the only person you always rely on,
널 절대 배신하지 않을 사람이란다
who'll never betray you.
내가 이 행복한 커플
잠시 빌려도 되지?
Uh, you mind if I, uh, borrow the happy couple?
나도 조언해줄 게 있어서 말야
I got a few words of wisdom myself.
그래
Okay.
행운을 비네!
Good luck!
버니가 저번 남자친구를
싫어했었거든
Bernie didn't like Jill's last boyfriend and...
그 앨 본 게 그 때가 마지막이었지
that's the last we saw of him.
여긴 어떻게 온 거니?
What are you doing here, Jill?
감옥에 있는 줄 알았는데
I thought you were in jail.
CIA하고 거래를 했어요
I made a deal with the CIA.
뭐? 거래라니?
What? What kind of a deal?
풀크럼에서 제 아버지를 어디에 숨기고 있는지 알려주시면
Look, Bernie, all you have to do is
tell us where FULCRUM is hiding my father
당신도 증인 보호 프로그램에
넣어드릴 게요
and we can offer you witness protection, too.
너 정말 멍청하게..
Oh, you stupid little...
도청기 했나?
Are you wired?
- 아뇨 안했어요
- 했지?
No, we're not. Are you wired?!
네 맞아요, 했어요
Yes, yes, we are.
들켰어, 가자
They're gone. Let's go.
안돼, 다짜고짜 들어가면
척 위장이 들통나잖아
No, we can't just blast in and blow Chuck's cover.
어머나
Oh, my.
우리 공주님 정말 행복해보여
Look how happy my baby is.
방해해서 미안해요
할 얘기가 있어서 왔어요
I'm sorry to interrupt, I just wanted to tell you
저녁 준비가 거의 다 됐어요
that dinner's almost ready, okay?
고마워요 주디
Thanks, Judy.
너무 괴롭히진 말아요, 버니
Don't torture them too much, Bernie.
질!
Jill!
이쪽으로 와!
Come on, come on, come on!
- 안녕하세요
Hi.
어떻게 오셨죠?
And you are?
전 척 사촌, 새라라고 해요
I'm Chuck's cousin, Sarah.
여긴 제 남자친구 존이고요
And this is my boyfriend, John.
미녀와 야수 커플이 따로 없네요
Talk about beauty and the beast, huh?
돈이 엄청 많으신 모양이에요
You must be loaded!
자, 다 농담이에요
Just a little friendly ribbing.
이제 우린 가족이에요
We're family now!
네, 가족이죠
Yeah, family.
- 여긴 사랑스런 제 아내, 주디에요
- 안녕하세요
This is my lovely wife, Judy.
Hello.
반갑습니다
Pleased to meet you.
네, 행운의 주인공들은 어딨나요?
Yeah, so, where's the lucky couple, hmm?
지금 버니 삼촌하고
같이 있어요
They're having a sit down with, uh, Uncle Bernie.
버니 그 친구가
지금쯤 척을 반쯤 죽여놨을 거예요
And if I know him, Chuck is dead meat by now.
케이시, 새라
3층이에요, 도와줘요
Casey, Sarah, third floor!We're in trouble!
날 죽이려는 건지
잡아먹으려는 건지 모르겠어요
I don't know if he wants to kill me or eat me!
위에 화장실이 있나요?
Is the bathroom upstairs, I hope?
실례할게요
Excuse me. Oh, uh...
저도 이만..
차를 정말 오래 탔거든요
I have to... we had a very long drive.
- 어디로 가지?
- 다락방으로 가자
Where are we going? The attic.
여기 말곤 도망칠 곳이 없어
The only way out is up.
케이시, 새라
Um, hey, Casey and Sarah,
다락방으로 왔어요
도와줘요, 큰일났어요
we're in the attic, we need some help- A lot of help!
창문!
Window!
질!
Jill!
삼촌, 이러지 마세요
Bernie, please don't do this.
우릴 쏘실 수 없을 거예요
You can't shoot us
그럼 가족 모두가 들을 거예요
because the whole family will hear it.
그래, 못 쏴
You're right; I can't.
하지만 죽을 때까지
패줄 순 있지
But I can beat you to death.
제가 죽지 않아도 되는
I was really hoping for a third option
3번째 방법은 없나요
that did not include death.
- 척, 괜찮아요?
- 네
Chuck, are you okay?
Yeah.
축하해, 척
Congratulations, Bartowski.
네 첫 번째 살인이야
It's your first confirmed kill.
살인이요?
Kill? No!
아뇨 아뇨, 아녜요
No, no, no, no.
난 죽인 적 없어요
I didn't kill anybody, okay?
그냥 죽은 거예요
사고였어요
He just died; it was an accident.
그래, 심장마비가 왔나봐
Well, maybe he had a heart attack.
근데 아까 그 동작은 뭐야?
What do you call your move, anyway?
무슨 동작이요?
What move?
아까 한 계집애 같은
포즈 말이야
The girlie pose I saw you in.
- 그게 뭐야?
- 모건이요
What do you call that?
The Morgan.
모건이요?
The Morgan?
여자 애들이 하도 때리고 괴롭히니까
He invented it in high school
모건이 고등학교 때 개발한 거예요
when girls were beating him up.
몸을 조금 굽혀서
You kind of duck a little bit,
중요한 부분을 가리는 거죠..
protect the important...
얼굴이랑 거기..
You know, your face and your...
이제 어떻게 해요?
What are we gonna do?!
저희 결혼식 계획을
들으시면서
We were telling him about our wedding plans,
계속 스카치를 마시셨는데
and he just kept knocking back scotches
어느샌가 잔뜩 취하셨더라고요
until the next thing we knew he was dead drunk.
전화해, 버니!
Uh, call me, Bernie!
그래요, 푹 쉬어요!
Yeah, get some rest!
알겠네
Okay.
집에 모셔다 드려야겠어요
Yeah, we should get him home. Okay.
- 갈게요 엄마
- 그래, 아가
Bye, Mom.
Bye, sweetheart.
- 갈게요 아빠
- 잘 가렴
Bye, Dad.
Bye, sweetie.
사랑한다, 잘 지내야 해
I love you.Take care of yourself.
다들 안녕히 계세요!
Good-bye, everyone!
- 잘 가게! 또 봐!
- 반가웠어!
Bye! See ya! Nice to meet you!
고맙습니다
Thanks!
버니는 저희가 잘 모셔다 드릴게요
We'll take care of Bernie.
잘했다, 살인자야
Way to go, killer.
방금 네 아버지 행방을 아는
You just offed the only person
유일한 사람을 죽인 거야
who knows where your dad is
미치겠네 정말
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
와, 모건
Wow, Morgan.
다들 오늘 멋있다
They look great.
멋있어 보일진 몰라도
멍청이가 된 기분이야
I may look good, but I feel like an idiot.
누가 이 꼴을
보기라도 했다간
Anybody sees or hears about this,
내 평판은 망가질 거야
my rep is ruined.
다들 진정 좀 할래?
내 말 믿어보라니까
Can you relax? Relax and trust me, please.
에멧을 떼어버릴 수 있는
유일한 방법이야
This is the only way
we're gonna get Emmett out of our hair.
고통 없인 얻는 것도
없단 말 몰라?
No pain, no gain, remember?
보시다시피 별탈 없이
As you can see, we're running
잘 운영되고 있습니다
smoother than a Swiss watch.
바이모어 직원들 중
이 사람들이 최고라고 할 수 있죠
You'll find no finer example of Buy More employees in the land.
파텔씨는 저희 지점
공인 컴퓨터 기술자 중 한명입니다
Mr. Patel here is one of our certified computer technicians.
정말 반갑습니다
Very pleased to meet you, sir.
전 에멧씨를 위해서라면
뭐든 할 준비가 되어있어요
And may I just say, I would do pretty much
anything for this man.
정말..
He is...
여기서 영웅같은 존재시거든요
...somewhat of a hero
around here.
이 친구가 아첨꾼(BROWNNOSER)이에요
A constant brownnoser.
하긴 피부부터가
갈색(BROWN)이니까
Well, he was born brown.
좀 더 말씀드릴게요 바이모어를 음료라고 한다면
May I go a step further and say that, uh, to me,
에멧씨는 바이모어를
Emmett is the straw
분발할 수 있게 도와주는
빨대같은 존재라고나 할까요
that gently stirs the Buy More drink.
전 여기서 수도없이
자위를 했었는데요
I can't tell you how many times I defiled myself at work.
에멧 씨 덕분에 고쳤어요
Emmett cured me of that.
이젠 집이나
차 안에서만 한답니다
Now I only violate myself at home or in the car.
하지만 절대 여기선 안해요
But never in the Nerd Herder.
정말 많이 나아졌죠 모든 게 다 에멧 씨의..
He has made such progress under Mr. Milbarge's...
지도 덕분입니다
...tutelage.
정말 자랑스러워요
We're all so proud.
캡틴으로서 할 일을 한 거죠
I'm your captain.
그럼요, 캡틴이시죠
Yes, captain, my captain.
저쪽도 보여드릴게요
Let me show you around.
모건, 네 말이 맞길
비는 게 좋을 거다
You better be right about this, Morgan.
네, 장군님
알겠습니다
Yes, General, I understand.
새라, 무슨 일이에요?
Sarah, what's happening?
질을 다시 감옥으로 보낼 거예요
We're moving Jill back to prison.
네? 안돼요
What? No, we can't...
그럴 순 없어요
아직 아빨 못 찾았잖아요
We can't send her back. We haven't found my father yet.
뭔가 알고 있을지도 모르고
거래도 했잖아요
She still might know somethingand we had a deal.
척, 미안하지만
작전도 실패했고
Chuck, I'm sorry but the mission was a bust
질 때문에 위험해지기만 했어요
and Jill only put us into more danger.
그건 걔 잘못이 아니죠!
That wasn't her fault!
버니 잘못이에요
질을 조종하고 배신한 거예요
It was Bernie! He manipulated
and betrayed her!
You know Jill.
질을 알잖아요
풀크럼 요원이라고요
She's a FULCRUM agent.
바로 그거에요
그니까 질이 필요한 거죠
Exactly! That's exactly why we need her.
풀크럼의 절차나
기밀 사항을 잘 알테니까요
She knows FULCRUM; their procedures and secrets.
질 때문에 죽을 뻔 했단 거 알아요
나도 유감이에요
Look, I know she tried to kill you, and I'm sorry
하지만 아빠를 구하려면
질이 꼭 필요해요
about that, but she is the best chance I have
at rescuing my father.He's out there somewhere
아빤 어딘가에 계시는데
어떻게 지내시는지
전혀 모르고 있다고요
and God only knows what's happening to him.
척, 내 말 들어요
Chuck, you have to realize
그냥 믿을 수 없는 사람이
있는 거예요
that there are some people that you just cannot trust.
새라
Sarah...
나도 알아요
I already know that.
나 아무도 믿지 않아요
I don't trust anyone.
새라만 빼고요
Except for you.
지금은 날 믿어줘요
And right now I need you to trust me.
질이 있어야만
아빠를 구할 수 있어요
Jill is the only way I'm gonna get my dad back.
척, 그래도 안돼요
Chuck, the answer is no.
모건
Hey, buddy.
척, 대체 어딨는 거야?
Chuck, where you been, man?
종일 전화했잖아
I've been calling you all day.
미안해, 친구
I'm sorry, buddy,
조금 바쁜 일이 있었어
I've just been a little a little busy, that's all.
있지, 여기 일이 좀 생겼는데
All right, well, listen, we have a situation here at the Buy More
네가 와서 좀 도와줘
and I could really use your help.
나 지금 외근중이라
I'm on an install.
당장은 못 도와줘
I- I can't help you right now.
알았어, 그럼 잠깐만
내 얘기 좀 들어봐
Okay, well, just bear with me for one second here, okay?
넌 네가 가장 믿지 않는 사람이
What do you do when the person
네가 가장 원하는 걸
줄 수 있다고 생각해?
that you think you can trust the least
can actually get you the thing you want the most?
내 생각엔 말이야
You know what, Morgan?
가끔은 그냥 그 사람을
믿어야 한다고 생각해
Sometimes you just need to trust a person.
무슨 일이 있어도 말이야
Do whatever it takes.
그래, 내 생각도 그랬어
Yeah, that's what I thought.
알았어
Roger that.
고마워 친구
Thanks, buddy.
미안해
I'm sorry.
널 다시 감옥으로 보낸대
They're sending you back to prison.
네 잘못도 아닌 걸 뭐
Well, it's not your fault.
그래도 마지막으로
식구들을 볼 수 있었잖아
At least I got to see my family one last time.
척, 못 도와줘서 미안해
I'm sorry I couldn't help you, Chuck.
괜찮아
It's okay.
버니 삼촌 일은 유감이야
I'm sorry about your Uncle Bernie.
모건 포즈가 그렇게
치명적일 줄은 몰랐어
I had no idea The Morgan was so lethal.
유머 감각이 그대로라 다행이다
I'm glad you haven't lost your sense of humor.
그 사람들 때문에 난 변했어
They changed me.
넌 변하지 않겠다고 약속해줘
Promise me that you won't let them change you.
최선을 다할게
I'll do my best.
이걸 끼고 있으니까 좋더라
I liked wearing this.
몇 시간 뿐이었지만 말야
Even if it was just for a few hours.
날 놔주지 않았을 거야
They were never gonna let me go,
네 아버질 찾았어도 말야
그랬겠지?
even if we found your dad, were they?
NSA, 풀크럼, CIA..
다 똑같아
NSA, FULCRUM, CIA- they're all the same.
다 거짓말을 해
They all lie.
너 또한 놔주지 않을 거야
They're not gonna let you go either, Chuck.
조심해
Watch your back.
스킵 씨, 앞으로 창창한
당신의 미래가 보이네요
Skip, I can tell you got a bright future ahead of you.
만나서 반가웠습니다
It's a pleasure meeting you.
It's all because of Emmett.
됐죠?
Well?
언제 그만둘 거예요?
When are you out of here?
부탁한 거 전부 다 했잖아요
We've done everything that you asked.
전부는 아니죠
대중들은 내게 절을 했지만
Not everything. The hoi polloi
have bowed to me, but now the king
왕이 아직 내 반지에
키스하지 않았어요
must kiss my ring.
왜 이래요, 진짜
Oh, come on.
그냥 머서 씨한테
마이크랑 직접 얘기하라고 해요
Man, why don't you just have Mr. Mercer speak
to Big Mike directly?
빅 마이크는 내가 필요하니까
Because Big Mike needs me.
절대 좋은 얘긴 안해줄 거예요
He'll never say kind words about me,
내가 떠나면 마이크가
다시 일을 해야 할테고
because if I were to leave, he has to work,
그럼 가게에
힘을 쏟기 시작할 거예요
and then he has to start expending
all of his energy on the store.
당신 어머니한테
힘 쏟는 것보단 낫죠
Rather than expending it on your mother.
알았어요, 알았어
기다려봐요
Okay, okay, hold on a second.
- 네?
- 그럼..
Yes? What-what, uh...
내가 어떻게 했으면 좋겠어요?
what do you want me to do?
Ah!
이걸 이용해서
내 얘기 좋게 해달라고 해요
Use this, and get him to say nice words about me.
머서 씨가 마이클이
고함치는 걸 들으면
When Mr. Mercer hears Michael rave,
지옥의 구덩이에서
날 구해줄 거고
he will finally release me from Satan's pit,
당신에겐 천국이 찾아오겠죠
and it will be your paradise.
문제가 있어요
Here's the thing.
빅 마이크가 다른 직원 얘길
Big Mike's never going to speak to me
나한테 할 리가 없다고요
about another employee, okay.
절대 바이모어 정책을
The man's like a wall of stone
위반할 사람이 아니에요
when it comes to breaching Buy More policy.
왜 이래요
Please.
모든 사람에겐 약점이 있어요
Every man has a weakness to exploit.
내 약점은 르네상스 박람회예요
Mine is Renaissance fairs.
누그럽게 만든 다음에
잘 구슬려 봐요
Just soften him up a little bit.
Grease his wheels.
Grease him?
구슬리라고요?
마이클이 항상
부족해 하는 게 뭘까요?
What is that Michael just cannot get enough of?
뭘 도와줄까, 아들?
What can I do for you, son?
치킨 데리야끼 샌드위치 사왔어요
Well I had an extra chicken teriyaki footlong
누가 먹고 싶어할 것 같아서요
I thought someone would be
interested in?
설마
Do tell.
5달러짜리 풋롱이에요
Five-dollar footlong.
Mmm.
맛있겠다
Oh, boy.
- 치킨 데리야끼로군
- 네
Chicken teriyaki. Yep.
버뱅크 안의
동양의 맛이랄까
A taste of the Orient in Burbank.
완벽히 조화를 이뤄서
풍미를 더해
The flavors melt together in perfect harmony.
나랑 네 엄마처럼 말이지
Just like me and your mama.
뭐 하나 여쭤봐도 돼요?
Can I ask you a question?
에멧에 대해
어떻게 생각하세요?
What do you think of Emmett?
모건, 네 앞에서
다른 직원 얘긴 하면 안돼
I really don't think I should
talk about other employees in front of you, Morgan.
절 직원이라고 생각하지 마시고요..
Well, don't-don't think of me as an employee...
아버지
Dad.
가족이라고 생각하고 말씀해보세요
You think of me as family.
그래 맞아
You're right.
가족을 믿지 못한다면..
If you can't trust family...
누굴 믿겠어?
who can you trust?
이게 마지막이겠지?
I guess this is good-bye, huh?
응
Yeah.
노력해줘서 고마워
Well, thanksb for trying.
으, 으, 미치겠네 정말
Ugh.
Ugh. Disgusting.
Oh, God.
풀크럼에서 온 전화면
If it's FULCRUM,
이게 아빠를 찾을 수 있는
마지막 기회에요
this could be my last chance to find out where they put my dad.
척, 받지마
Don't answer that,
Bartowski.
버니다, 말해
Bernie. Talk to me.
오리온을 옮길 거야
빌이 모두 기지로 오래
We're moving Orion. Bill wants all agents
back to base.
아빨 다른 곳으로 옮긴대요
They're moving my dad,
모든 요원들에게 기지로
오라고 지시했어요
and they want all the agents back at the base.
알았어요, 계속 통화해요
Okay, keep him on the line.
전화를 추적 해볼게요
We're going to trace his call.
그래, 알았다
곧 기지로 돌아가겠다
Yeah, yeah, I'll, uh,
I'll be back at the base pronto,
그 전에 의논할 일이 있어
but there's a couple of things I'd like to discuss.
의논? 무슨 일인데?
Discuss? Discuss what?
뭐긴 뭐야, 그거 말이야
You know, you know, stuff.
의논할 게 있다고
Stuff to discuss.
내 보수 말이야
Uh... particularly my salary.
당신 보수?
Your salary?
요즘 밤새 일했단 말이야
I've been burning the midnight oil,
자네도 내가 해낸
일들에 대해 잘 알잖아
and if you ask me, my work speaks for itself.
버니, 대체 무슨 소릴 하는 거야?
Bernie, what the hell are you talking about?
또, 우리가 해야 할 얘기가 있어
Also, uh, there are other pertinent things
that we could talk about.
예를 들어서 말이야..
Including, but not limited to...
치과 보험이랑 휴가 같은 거
the dental plan and vacation days.
그리고 체육관 멤버십도 괜찮고
And I could use a gym membership.
자네 내 몸 잘 알잖아?
그래
Have you looked at me? Excellent.
좋아, 기지에서 마저 얘기하지
끊겠네
Good. We'll talk about it at the base. Bye.
치과 보험?
Dental plan?
- 멍청한 놈
- 데스테파노 1600번지야
Moron. Okay, it looks like the call came
from 1600 Destefano Court.
멀홀랜드 근처에 있는
사무실 빌딩이야
It's an office building somewhere off Mulholland.
그 빌딩 알아요
I- I know that building.
리더쉽 강화 훈련 본사예요
It's the headquarters for the Strength Leadership Corporation.
CEO, 경영자 훈련 세미나를 여는데
They run CEO and management training seminars,
사실 풀크럼 요원을
스카우트 하려는 거예요
but really that's just a front
for a FULCRUM recruiting facility.
아빨 왜 거기로 데려가?
Why-why would they take my dad there? Because
그 건물 8층에 수감 시설이 있으니까
they have holding cells forv prisoners on the eighth floor.
서두르는 게 좋겠어, 가자
We better hustle. Let'go.
나도 데려가요
가본 적 있어요
Take me with you. I've been there before.
빌딩 주변 지리도 잘 알고
I know my way around the building
보안 시스템도 알아요
and the security system.
그래요, 도움이 될 거예요
Guys, we need her.
척, 그 누구도 믿어선 안돼
Chuck, you can't trust anyone.
따분한 사무실 건물 같아 보여도
This may look like a boring office building,
풀크럼이 운영하는 곳이야
but it's run by FULCRUM.
케이시, 사실이에요
Casey, she's right,
사무 직원들이 아니고
these are not pencil pushers.
풀크럼 암살자들이에요
These are FULCRUM assassins.
진정해, 살인자 양반
Relax, killer.
일이 꼬이면
또 모건 포즈하면 되잖아
The going gets rough, you can always deploy The Morgan.
척, 보안 시스템에 들어갔어요
Chuck, we've tapped into the security feed.
내가 다 지켜보고 있으니까
아무 일 없을 거예요
I'm watching
your every move. You're going to be safe.
안내 데스크로 가서
When you get to the desk,
감사하러 왔다고 해
tell him you're here for Auditing.
뭘? 회계 같은 거야?
What, is that like accounting?
아니, 시험하는 거야
No, it's like testing.
어떻게 오셨죠?
Can I help you gentleman?
감사하러 왔습니다
Yes, we're here for Auditing.
2층입니다
계단으로 올라가시면 됩니다
Second floor. Up the stairs.
잘했어, 이제
시험 센터를 지나서
Okay, now,
go past the testing center
엘리베이터로 가
down the hallway to the elevator.
수감 시설은 8층에 있어
The holding cells are on the eighth floor.
오른쪽으로 가서
Okay, make a right
복도를 쭉 내려가
and go down the hallway.
여긴 어떻게 오셨죠?
Hey, what are you doing here?
아, 그게..
Uh, we're, uh...
감사하러 왔습니다
we're here for the Auditing.
누구랑 약속하셨죠?
Who set the meeting?
도른호퍼 씨라고 해요
Tell him Mr. Dornhoffer.
도른호퍼 씨요
Mr. Dornhoffer.
잘못 오셨네요
You're on the wrong floor.
- 8층이라고 들었는데요
- 8층이요
Oh, we were told eight.
Eight.
아닌가요? 그렇군요
No? Okay.
죄송해요, 하지만
Sorry about that. But it's a...
이런 실수도 할 수 있는 거죠 뭐
it's a common mistake I'm sure.
척, 그 사람이
하자는 대로 해
Chuck, just do what he says.
다른 방법을 찾아볼게
I'll find another way to get to your dad.
늦으셨네요
You two are late.
죄송합니다
Sorry.
시험을 보기 전에
짧은 비디오를 보겠습니다
Before the test, we have a brief video
for you to watch.
풀크럼에 오신 걸 환영합니다
Welcome to FULCRUM.
미래의 문제를
오늘 해결합니다
Solving tomorrow's problems...today.
우린 위험한 시대에
살고 있습니다
We live in a dangerous world.
그래서 당신은
세상에 도움이 되고 싶습니다
And you want to do something about it.
그럴 능력이 있으신가요?
Do you have what it takes?
곧 알아보도록 하죠
We're about to find out.
행운을 빕니다
전우 여러분
Good luck on the test, comrades.
시작하세요
You may begin.
어떻게 하지?
What do we do?
시험을 보는 수 밖에 없어
You have to take the test, Chuck.
아니면 의심할 거야
You don't want to raise their suspicions.
이런 거 진짜 싫어
I hate these tests.
난 컨닝 안해요
I'm not gonna cheat.
농담이지?
You're kidding, right?
아뇨, 농담 아닌데요
No, I'm not kidding.
이 두 사람이 8층에
있는 걸 발견했습니다, 버기 씨
Found them on the eighth floor, Mr. Bergey.
길을 잃었고, 감사를
하러 왔다고 했습니다
Said they were lost, were here for Auditing.
정체가 뭔지 알아보도록 하지
Well, let's find out who they really are.
아버지를 구하러 온 모양이군
???? father ,charles.
에멧, 솔직히 말해서
나 좀 놀랐어요
I must say, Emmett, I'm impressed.
매장은 문제 없이 잘 운영되고 있고
The store's running smoothly.
직원들은 이상한 이유였지만
당신을 존경하고요
The employees, for some strange reason, respect you.
이제 빅 마이크만 만나보면 되겠네요
Now if I could only find Big Mike.
참, 오늘 하루 쉬세요
Oh, he took the day off.
네? 마이클이 왜요?
What? Why would
Michael take the day off? Oh.
하지만 여기 있는 거나 다름 없어요
You're looking at him.
자
Please.
들어 보세요
Listen.
에멧은 좋은 직원이지
Emmett's a good worker.
에멧 덕분에 내가
Thanks to Emmett,
일주일에 세 번 낚시도 하고
I can fish three times a week
매장도 잘 운영되는 거지
and the store never misses a beat.
사실 오늘도 그만 일하고
In fact, I'm-I'm gonna take the rest of the day off,
- 오후부터 낚시하러 갈 거야
- 그만해요
do a little fishing this afternoon. Okay.
빅 마이크를 평가하러 왔는데
I came down here to evaluate
낚시를 하러 갔단 거예요?
Big Mike and he's off fishing?
좋아요, 에멧
Well, Emmett,
그동안 마이크 자리를
원해왔었죠
you've been gunning for Mike's job all year.
당신이 맡아요
It's yours.
행운을 빌어요
Good luck...
매니저 님
...store manager.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
축하합니다
Congratulations.
시험 점수가 아주 인상적이더군요
Your test score was very impressive.
우리 세미나 리더이신
빌 버기 씨께서
Bill Bergey, our seminar leader,
직접 만나뵙고 싶어 하십니다
would like to meet you.
빌 버기는 요원 모집
총 책임자예요
Bill Bergey's head of recruiting.
척 아버지가 어딨는지
알 거예요
He'll know where Chuck's dad is.
- 전 어땠나요?
- 유감입니다만 낙제하셨어요
How did I do? I'm sorry, sir.
You failed.
사실, 저희 세미나 역사상
최하점에 속하세요
In fact, I'm afraid
you had one of the lowest scores we've ever had.
절 따라오세요, 카마이클 씨
Come with me, Mr. Carmichael.
Um...
저기, 제 친구가
머리는 잘 안돌아가도
you know, what-what my friend lacks
in the intellect department,
몸 쓰는 건 잘하거든요
he does make up for in brawn.
여기에도 박스나
무거운 장비 같은 거
Certainly, you must have some kind of a job
옮기는 그런 일도 있지 않나요?
moving boxes or heavy equipment?
따라오세요, 카마이클 씨
Come with me, Mr. Carmichael.
네
Okay.
케이시, 앉아
Casey, stand down.
일단 그냥 보내
Just let Chuck go.
시계로 추적하면 되잖아
We can track him using his watch.
제가 도와 드릴게요
이쪽입니다
May I help sir?
This way
이쪽입니다
케이시 요원
Agent Casey.
나야, 워커
Talk to me, Walker.
여긴 정리됐어
I'm all clear.
알았어, 척은 15층에 있어
Okay, Chuck's on the 15th floor.
빌딩 서쪽 끝으로 가고 있어
He's heading to the far west side of the building.
거긴 보안 구역이야
It's a secure area.
출입 카드가 필요할 거야
You're going to need a way in.
- 안녕하세요
- 어서 오게
Ah, hello, welcome.
Hi.
- 빌 버기라고 하네
- 찰스 카마이클입니다
I'm Bill Bergey. Charles Carmichael.
잘 왔어
자, 앉게
Nice to meet you. Please sit down.
고맙습니다
Thank you.
그래..
So...
자네 정체를 알고 있어, 찰스
I know who you really are, Charles.
아버지가 오리온이지
That your father is Orion.
오리온이요?
Orion?
그게 무슨 말씀이신지
Uh, I'm not really tracking.
전 전혀 모르겠네요
I don't know what you're talking about.
전 여기 세미나를
들으러 왔는데요
I'm-I'm just here for the... for the seminar.
리더십 퍼스트, 맞죠?
Leadership first, right?
그랬나?
그렇담 운이 없군
Oh, well, thenyou're out of luck.
세미나 자리가 꽉 찼거든
The seminar is full.
도청기 달았나?
Are you wearing a wire?
도청기라뇨 말도 안돼요
That's preposterous.
도청기 달았어?
Are you wearing a wire?
네, 네, 맞아요
Yes, yes, I am.
척?
Chuck?
케이시, 척이 붙잡혔어
들어갈게
Okay, Casey, they've got him. I'm going in.
나도 데려가요
You have to take me with you.
믿어도 된다고 어떻게 확신하죠?
And how do I know I can trust you?
못하죠. 하지만
내 도움이 필요하잖아요
You don't. But you need my help,
척에겐 우리 뿐이고요
and we're the only chance Chuck's got.
아버질 구하겠다고 여길 나타나다니
큰 실수를 했어
You made a big mistake coming here to rescue him.
침입자가 있다
15층이다
Intruder alert, 15th floor.
버기 씨
침입자가 있답니다
Sir, we have a break in.
침입자 발생
Security breech.
잘 지켜
Watch him.
도망치려고 하면 쏴버려
He tries to escape, shoot him.
솔직히 난 도망칠 생각없어요
Guys, look, honestly,I'm not going to try and escape.
스카우트의 명예를 걸고
맹세해요
Scout's honor.
CIA가 침입했다
모두 밖으로 피신하라
CIA intrusion- get everyone out.
나가야 해
We're out of here.
아무리 생각해도
난 시험 통과했어
Looks like I passed that test.
새라는요?
Where's Sarah?
너 구하러 오다가
She came to rescue you,
요원들한테 걸려서
꼼짝 못하고 있어
got pinned down by some FULCRUM agents.
빨리 가서 우리 아빠 구해요
Okay... let's go get my dad.
네가 시험을 잘봤을진 몰라도
나가면 다 소용 없어
Your test-taking skills won't do any good out there.
컴퓨터로 어느 방에
계신지 찾아봐
Get on the computer.
Find out which room he's in.
질, 척이 어느 사무실에 있어요?
Jill, which office is Chuck in?
질?
Jill?
케이시, 질이 도망쳤어
Casey, Jill escaped.
가자! 서둘러!
Let's go, let's go.
하드 드라이브 지워!
Destroy the hard drives!
11번 방에 전화해서
오리온을 블랙 락으로 옮기라고 해
Go to cell 11- move Orion to Black Rock.
서둘러, 오리온을 지켜야 돼
No time to waste- Orion's too valuable.
블랙 락에서 다시 얘기하지
We'll talk again at Black Rock.
컴퓨터에서 떨어져
Get away from that computer now.
난 아버질 되찾고 싶을 뿐이야
I just want my father back.
좋은 소식과 나쁜 소식이 있어
Good news, bad news, Charles.
좋은 소식은 네 아버지가
너무 중요해서 죽일 수 없단 거야
The good news is that your father
is too valuable for us to kill.
나쁜 소식은?
The bad news?
넌 안 중요하단 거지
You're not.
그니까 어서 컴퓨터에서..
Now, step away from the...
Whoa!
정말 그 포즈가 효과가 있나?
What is it with that move?
도와줘
Help.
제발 도와줘
어서
Oh, God.
Help me.
도와줘요
Help!
어서요! 누구 없어요? 도와줘요
Please, please, somebody, I need help!
- 올려줘!
- 노력 중이에요
Pull me up!
I'm trying!
최선을 다하고 있다고요
어서요, 우리 아빠 어딨어요
Look, please, please, tell me where my father is.
말 안해주면
떨어뜨릴 거야?
Or what, you'll drop me?
안 떨어뜨려요
어떻게 그런 끔찍한 일을 해요
I'd never drop you- that's a horrible thing
to do to somebody.
정말?
Really?
네, 여기 15층이잖아요
Yeah, it's a 15-story fall.
여기서 떨어져 죽는 건 끔찍하잖아요
It's an awful way to die.
올려줘, 말해줄게
Pull me up- I'll talk.
꽉 잡아요
Hold on.
버텨야 돼, 척
내가 잡았어
Hold on, Chuck, I got you.
미끄러워, 서둘러
미끄러지겠어
No, he's slipping. Hurry, he's slipping.
버텨요
Hold on.
세상에
Oh, God... oh, God.
고마워
Thank you.
응
Yeah.
빨리 아빠를 구하자
Look, we have to get to my dad now.
8층이야, 어서 가자
Eighth floor- let's go.
??
낙제 시켜줘서 고맙다
That's for flunking me.
- 나 보고 싶었어?
- 응, 무지
Miss me? Yeah, immensely.
질이 도망쳤어
Jill's gone.
- 어떻게 된 거야?
- 그 사람이 날 공격했는데
What happened? Well, he attacked me.
모건 포즈를 취했더니
창문 밖으로 날아갔어
I did The Morgan, and he flew out the window.
이틀 동안 두명이나 죽인 거야
Two kills in two days, Chuck.
모건 포즈덕에 정말 살인자가 됐어
Wow, that Morgan move is real killer.
아빠!
Dad!
너무 늦었어
We're too late.
다신 못 찾는 거지?
I'm never going to find him, am I?
잠깐만, 아까 내가
한번도 못 들어본 곳으로
Wait, I overhead them say that they were moving your father
옮긴단 말을 들었어
블랙 락이랬어
to a place I never heard of, a place called Black Rock.
맙소사
Oh, my God.
어디로 옮겼는지 알겠어
I know where they're taking him.
블랙 락은 프로토콜 7의
암호명이야
Black Rock is a code name for Protocol 7,
바스토우에 있는
풀크럼 기밀 기지를 말하는 거야
a secret FULCRUM base in Barstow.
그걸 어떻게 알아, 척?
How do you know that, Chuck?
알고 싶지 않을 거야
You don't want to know.
척, 내 말 들려요?
Chuck, can you hear me?
나 8층에 있어요
I'm on the eighth floor.
이미 아빠를 피신시켰어요
They've already evacuated my dad.
알았어요, 꼼짝 말고 있어요
Okay, hold tight.
그 쪽으로 갈게요
We're on our way. Okay, come on.
뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
움직이지 말아봐
Don't move.
질, 거래 같은 건 없었어
Look, Jill, there was no deal.
내가 거짓말 한 거야
왜냐하면, 난 지금까지
I lied to you because, at the time,
아빨 찾기 위해서라면
뭐든 하려고 했었으니까
I was willing to do whatever it took
to find my father, but not anymore.
하지만 지금은 아냐
네가 약속을 지켰으니까
You held up your side of the bargain,
이젠 내가 지킬 차례야
and I'm going to hold up mine.
내가 변하지 않겠다고 했었지
변하지 않을게
I told you I wouldn't let them change me, and I won't.
고마워, 척
Thank you, Chuck.
새라랑 케이시가
오기 전에 어서 가
Look, you should go before they get here.
갈게
Okay.
하지만, 질
But, Jill,
이젠 혼자 힘으로 지내야 될 거야
look, you're going to be all alone out there.
친구도, 돈도
그 어떤 것도 없이
No friends, no money, nothing.
이거면 도움이 될 거야
This is worth a lot.
케이시가 날 죽이려 들겠지
Casey's probably going to kill me.
난 항상 너한테
반지 주는 걸 꿈꿨었어
I always dreamt of giving you a ring, Jill...
이런 식은 아니었지만
just not like this.
정말 그 사람들
믿어도 되는 거야?
You're sure you can trust them, right?
가
Go
매장직으로 돌아온 걸 환영해요
Welcome back to gen pop, Michael.
행운을 빌어요
Good luck.
네가 그런 거 알아, 모건
I know it was you, Morgan.
나한테 상처를 주다니
You broke my heart.
내 가슴을 찢어놨어
내가 모건 엄마랑 데이트 하는 동안엔
I don't want anything to happen to him
아무 일도 없어야 해
as long as his mom and I are dating.
어떻게 질 로버츠를 놓칠 수가 있나?
How could you let
Jill Roberts get away?
죄송합니다 장군님
건물로 데려갈 수 밖에 없었습니다
I'm sorry, General- I took her
inside the building because I didn't have a choice.
그럼 스티브 바토스키가
어딨는지도 모르고
So, not only do we have no idea where Steve Bartowski is,
우리의 모든 비밀을 아는
we have a FULCRUM agent
풀크럼 요원이
밖을 돌아다니고 있단 거군
who knows all of our secrets running free.
척은 어딨나?
Where is Chuck now?
바이모어로 가는 중입니다
He's on his way to the Buy More.
그 바보 녀석 어디
어두운 구멍에 확 빠뜨리고 올까요
Permission to drop the twerp into a deep dark hole, General.
- 그렇게 하게
- 네?
Granted.
Huh?
다 끝났네
인간 인터섹트 프로젝트가
It's over- the Human Intersect project
관리하기가
너무 힘들어졌어
has become too hard to control.
이젠 더 이상 팀과 척 중에
I can't afford to wonder anymore
어느 쪽이 책임을 져야 할지
생각하고 있을 겨를이 없네
if this team or Chuck Bartowski is a liability.
무슨 말씀을
하시는 거예요, 장군님?
What are you saying, General?
프로젝트를 중지하는 거네
I'm shutting down this project.
척은 수감시설로 가게 될 거야
Chuck's going into lockdown.
일단 워싱턴으로 갔다가
He'll be taken to Washington
최종적으론 보안 시설로
들어가게 될 거야
and put into a secure facility once and for all.
멍청이 작전이 끝이라고?
Operation Moron is over?
장군님, 실수 하시는 거예요
You're making a mistake, General.
이미 결정을 내렸네
워커 요원
I have made my decision, Agent Walker.
척이 그냥 받아들이진 않을 거예요
Chuck isn't going to go down without a fight.
받아들이게 만들어야지
That's why there won't be one.
무슨 말씀이세요?
What do you mean?
척은 자넬 믿지
Chuck trusts you, Sarah.
자네가 절대 배신하지
않을 거라 믿고 있어
He believes you would never betray him.
그걸 이용해
Use that.
척한테 가보게
Go to Chuck.
아버지를 이송 중에 구해냈고
Tell him that we intercepted his father
지금 기지로 오는 중이라고 해
while being transported and that he's back at Castle.
나 믿어선 안될 사람을 믿었어
I trusted the wrong person, Chuck.
케이시 요원은
여기서 기다리고 있게
Agent Casey will be waiting here.
케이시는 척에게
진정제를 놓고
He will tranq Chuck.
척을 이송할 팀이
올 때까지 기다리게
Then, he will wait for the extraction team
to arrive for his transfer.
이상이네
That is all.
어떻게 멀쩡히 서서
How can you just stand there
- 아무 말 안할 수가 있어?
- 장군님 말씀이 옳아
and say nothing?
Beckman's right.
척은 숨어 지내는 게
제일 안전해
Safest place for Chuck is underground.
풀크럼이 질을 찾아내면
What do you think is going to happen
어떻게 될지 생각해 봤어?
when FULCRUM finds Jill, anyway?
좋은 소식이 있어요
We have good news.
나중에 해도 되죠?
Can it wait?
컴퓨터 고치러 가야 되는데
Computer emergency.
아버지 일이에요
It's about your father.
찾았어요
We found him.
네? 어떻게요?
What? How?
어디 계세요?
Where is he?
풀크럼이 피신시킬 때
정찰팀에서 중간에서
One of our recon teams intercepted his transport
아버지를 구해냈어요
as FULCRUM was moving him.
지금 기지로 오고 계세요
He's back at the Castle.
이제 안전하세요, 척
He's safe, Chuck.
다 끝났어요
It's all over.
미안해요
I owe you an apology.
왜요?
Why?
더 이상 새라를 믿을 수 없다고
I was beginning to think
생각하는 중이었어요
that I couldn't trust you anymore, Sarah.
질 말이 옳을지도 모른다고
That maybe Jill was right,
CIA는 날 놔주지 않을 거라고
that the CIA was never going to let me go,
나보단 자기들
잇속 챙기기 급급할 거라고요
that they would always put
their best interests ahead of mine.
하지만 당신은 아녜요
But not you.
항상 날 지켜줬어요
You've always looked out for me.
고마워요
Thank you.
시계 벗어요
Take off your watch.
왜요?
Why?
다 거짓말이니까요
Because it's all a lie.
아버지 못 찾았어요
Your dad is still out there.
장군님이 나한테 당신을
Beckman sent me to get you
기지로 데리고 오라고 명령했어요
to bring you back to the Castle.
척을 가둘 거래요
They're going to take you underground.
도망쳐야 해요
We have to run.
날 위해서
명령을 어기는 거예요?
You're disobeying orders for me?
이건 반역죄예요, 새라
You're committing treason, Sarah.
감옥에 가야할 수도 있어요
You could go to jail.
나도 알아요
I know.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
팎읔襟俚캥莉
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
뻑短속흙